mig.me 2015-06-15

# Privacy | migme

## Introduction and Scope

In this Privacy Policy, we (Mig33 Pte Ltd, headquartered in Singapore) describe how we use personally identifiable information about you that we collect through our website at [mig.me](http://mig.me/), through our migme software, through your use of our platform services, and through our customer support, [contact@mig.me](mailto:contact@mig.me). This Privacy Policy does not apply to any other data, including, without limitation, data that we collect offline about our customers, data about our employees or data that others collect on websites that are linked to our website.

## About Children

This website is for adults only. In particular, it is notintended for children under the age of 13. We do not knowingly collect personally identifiable information via this website from visitors in this age group. We encourage parents to talk to their children about their use of the Internet and the information they disclose to websites.

## Advertising

migme displays targeted advertisements.

  * When an advertiserbooks an ad placement in migme, they are given the opportunity to choose their audience by location, demographics, gender and any other non-personally identifiable information we receive or collect from you.
  * We do not sell, trade or rent personally identifiable information about our users to advertisers, without our users' consent. However, by interacting with or viewing an ad you are consenting to the possibility that the advertiser may make the assumption that you meet the targeting criteria used to display the ad. Please note that this Privacy Policy in no way restricts or limits our collection and use of aggregate information which is data we collect about your use of our website or about a group or category of services or users, from which individual identities or other personally identifiable information has been removed.
  * migme may use cookies, web beacons or other technologies to record information about what ads your browser is shown, as well as what ads you click on and other actions you take on our website and services.
  * Advertisers may sometimes place their own cookies on your computer in order to make their ads more effective.
  * Please remember that any personal information you provide on the linked pages, ads you click on or other websites is subject to a third party's privacy policy. This Privacy Policy does not apply to such linked websites, ads you click on or other website, and we are not responsible for the content or privacy and security practices and policies of these websites or any other websites that are linked to from our website. We encourage you to learn about their privacy and security practices and policies before providing them with personal information.
  * Also, third party ad networks may serve ads on our website or provide ads via our services and/or otherwise place cookies, web beacons or other devices or technologies on our website (or via our services) to enable them to automatically collect non-personal information about you and your visits to our website and to other websites, your IP address, your ISP and the browser you use to visit our website and other websites. Information collected may be used, among other things, to analyze data, to deliver content and advertising on our website or other websites (including content and advertising that is targeted to your interests), to determine the popularity of certain content, and to better understand the usage and visitation of our website and the other websites tracked by these third parties. This Privacy Policy does not apply to, and we are not responsible for, cookies or clear GIFs in third party ads, and we encourage you to check the privacy policies of advertisers and/or ad services to learn more about their use of cookies and other technologies. If you would like more information about this practice and your choices as it relates to adnetworks, please visit [www.networkadvertising.org](http://www.networkadvertising.org/).

## Types of Data We Collect, Collection Methods, Combination of Data

Through the website, we receive data that you actively submit and data that we track passively.

**Actively Submitted Data:** You actively send information to us if and when you sign up with us a user, register for our Merchant Program, respond to us or otherwise contact us. Depending on your choices, you may send us personally identifiable information such as your email address, name, mailing address, phone number, date of birth, gender, password, as well as credit card information.

**Passively Tracked Data:** When you visit the website, we also track information abouthow our website is used by you through "cookie" technology. Cookies are pieces of information that a web site transfers to your computer's hard disk for record-keeping purposes. Cookies save your passwords, purchases, and preferences while you are using our website. The use of cookies is common on major websites and most web browsers are set to accept cookies. You may set your browser to refuse cookies but this may mean that you will not be able to take full advantage of the features available on our website. We also collect information regarding your use of our service, including calling records and records of messages sent and received.

**Combinations:** Unless you also actively submit personal information such as your name or address, passively tracked data does not typically allow us to identify you personally (even though it can theoretically be done, we do not have the means or an interest to find out who you are unless you identify yourself voluntarily through an active submission of data). However, to the extent permitted by applicable law, we reserve the right to combine passively tracked data with personal data that you actively submit.

## Purposes of Data Collection

We collect information from you so that we can manage and administer the services we provide to you; administer your account; respond to your questions; solve any technical support problems; communicate with you about any modifications, upgrades or enhancements to our service; determine what sorts of services are likely to be most useful for you and to further develop our understanding of customers' needs; ensure your compliance with our Terms of Use; and carry out a statistical analysis of the use of our service.

## Disclosure of Data

We keep your personally identifiable information confidential and we disclose it only as follows:

  * Our employees and independent contractors have access to some of your data, including your personally identifiable information, for the purpose of helping us run our business. They access and use data subject to our instructions, on a "need to know" basis and under confidentiality and security obligations.
  * We may share data with affiliated companies.
  * We may share your information with trusted third-party service providers and other business partners, which we engage and obligate to process your data only on our behalf or on behalf of joint purposes, e.g., in support of delivering information, products or services to you.
  * We may also share your personally identifiable information to respond to law enforcement requests, court orders or other legal process or if we believe that such disclosure is necessary to investigate, prevent or respond to illegal activities, fraud, physical threats to you or others or as otherwise required by any applicable law or regulation.
  * We may share or transfer your information in connection with a prospective or actual sale, merger, transfer or other reorganization of all or parts of our business.
  * We freely use and disclose data received in anonymous form.
  * Before we disclose your personally identifiable data for other reasons, we will first obtain your consent, for example via email, click-through, an online opportunity to opt-out or otherwise.

## Security

We take reasonable steps to protect personally identifiable information from loss, misuse, and unauthorized access, disclosure, alteration, or destruction. But, you should keep in mind that no Internet transmission is ever completely secure or error-free. In particular, messages sent to or from this website may not be secure.

It is important that you maintain the confidentiality of any password, PIN or other ID check information in order to keep your personally identifiable information secure. Please notify us as soon as possible if you suspect that there is any unauthorized use of your account or there is any other breach of security.

## Access to information

If you would like to know what personal information we hold about you or if you would like to correct any of the information that we hold, please [contact us](mailto:contact@mig.me).

## Opt-Out, Communication Preferences

You may modify your communication preferences and/or opt-out from specific communications at any time. Please specify and adjust your preferences by emailing us at [contact@mig.me](mailto:contact@mig.me).

## Changes to This Privacy Policy

This Privacy Policy is effective August 31, 2007. We reserve the right to amend it from time to time and if we change it materially, we will post a revised version on this website. Please check back periodically, and especially before you provide any personally identifiable information to us.

## Terms of Use

Note also that your use of our website is subject to our Terms of Use, which contain disclaimers, limitations of liability, a choice of California law, and consent to the jurisdiction of State and federal courts in California.

## Contact Us

Please feel free to contact us with any comments, questions, complaints or suggestions you might have regarding the information practices described in this privacy policy. You may send us an e-mail at [contact@mig.me](mailto:contact@mig.me).
